musicbuzz.info 2014-06-25

# Musicbuzz Privacy Policy

## Privacy Statement For Musicbuzz.info

Musicbuzz.info has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this web site: Musicbuzz.info

## Request

We do release to spread good music.   
We don't want to hurt the music industry or any person.   
If you like any album, Please buy it.   
If you don't buy an album you like, you kill the music you like.

## What Information We Collect

We Have Several Areas Where Members Can Submit Information To Us, And We Also Have Features That Automatically Collect Information From Our Members And Other Users.

## Information You Provide To Us

We Have Certain Areas Where We Ask You To Provide Information To Us:

##  User Registration 

You may register with us to use some of our member only features on our site. We may also offer the option for you to register with us or sign up for our mailing list without having to use any other product or service. During registration, you provide your "contact information" (which identifies you and how we can contact you, such as your name and email address) as well as certain demographic information (which describes certain information about you, such as your country of residence). You may be asked to enter a e-mail address and password. We may also ask you to provide additional information about your music preferences, so that we can cater to those preferences. The registration information that you provide will be reflected in the "Musiqbuzz" section of the service. 

Affiliate sites or sponsors in offering contests or sweepstakes, we may share (provide and receive) information with them. 

## Third Party Cookies

Third party cookies in the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique 'cookie' on your browser.

We use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our web site, cookies received with banner ads and letter ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information. Some customer data is shared with the advertising companies.

##  External Links

Musiqbuzz.com contains links of other sites on the internet. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of web sites we link to. We do make an effort to avoid linking to known 'adult' and 'porn' sites. **Musiqbuzz.com is a family web site.**

##  Changes To Our Privacy Policy

To the maximum extent permitted by applicable law, we reserve the right to change or replace this privacy policy at any time and from time to time without prior notice to or the consent of any person. Any changes or replacement will be posted at this site.

To get in touch with us, Please E-Mail At : admin@musiqbuzz.com, We Will Reply Within 48 Hours.
